{
    "id": "0a1b81a06a2f4f5e9a77d020a792a36b",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Prepositions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you knew the answer why didn’t you tell me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "In case"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not go to their party, …………………………. they invite me.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if...not.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. he mends his ways, he will be in trouble.",
            "description": "Unless means if...not...",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "If not"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not go …………………………. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "without",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. he received the message, he started.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "Hardly had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he is rich, he is not respected.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Even if",
                "If",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. you forbid me, I will go.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Even if",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If I help him it is ……………………………. I like him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "because",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. had he returned than he was off again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "As soon as",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Scarcely had he gone to bed, ……………………………. someone knocked at the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "before",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He became angry …………………………….. I had said a word.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "than",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is as good …………………………… not better than that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}